There's no question...
This guy is an absolute monster.
Hey... What the hell are you?
A girl just went inside you, right?
That's not a normal transformation, is it?
Not yet, Shuichi.
We've only got one chance.
Come on out.
If we're doing this, it's got to be point-blank!
Wow...
That's pretty cool.
What is this thing?
Wha--
Huh?
I see... There were two of you.
What the hell, Madoka!
Don't leave us out of the fun, boss.
Well, you've probably figured it out, but...
You can't win.
You're all gathering coins together, right?
Well, I don't know why you're after the coins...
...but you're going to start
gathering them for me now.
You've got to be joking!
Just listen to what I have to say.
Our team's goal is simple.
We gather coins, and I gain power.
And with that power,
I make your dreams come true.
I don't care if it's money, cars, or women--
If there's something you want, just tell me.
I will get it.
Pretty simple, all right...
We like it simple.
The world is too complicated.
They make it complicated
on purpose so idiots lose out.
I want to make idiots,
like my friends here, happy.
They're important to me, see?
By the way, I heard you showed
my pal Morita a real good time.
As the boss, I can't let it slide
when one of my pals gets roughed up.
I'm real sorry, but one of
you is going to have to die.
You guys can pick who it'll be.
I'll handle killing them.
What the hell?! Who would do--
If you don't like it, I'll kill all of you.
You bastard...
Question.
What is it?
You just punched two members of our group.
If one of those two ends up
being dead, how will that work?
Excellent question, freckles.
I still want you to pick one.
You might say it's your rite of passage--
To make sure you're
a bunch of shitheads like us.
As a reward for such a great question,
I'll take you out of the running, freckles.
Wha--?!
I can tell when I look in your eyes--
You're one of us.
I'll give you some time to talk things over.
Be real with yourself,
and throw away all your fancy ideals--
That's the kind of pal I want.
Well, I'm glad those two are alive.
Who the hell are they?
He's so ruthless, but he keeps
talking about how important his pals are.
His pals are important to him,
and our pals are important to us.
It's ironic, but we're
kind of the same like that.
Well, Shuichi?
Can you smell them?
They're in that dry riverbed,
about 200 meters off.
I think they're watching us.
As I thought.
We have some bad luck, huh?
Getting caught by someone like that...
So? What do we do now?
There's only one thing to do.
I'm going to fight them.
It's true. We can't offer up one of our own.
Don't be an idiot. There's no way you can win.
We got beat this bad by just one of them!
And there's way more this time!
We can't run! You've got to face facts!
If we fight, we're all dead!
Shut up, Ikeuchi!
No, I won't shut up!
You saw it, didn't you?!
They really kill people!
Ikeuchi is right.
I think our only option
is to offer up a sacrifice.
Clair!
Well, what can we do?
Their demands are pretty clear,
not a lot of room for negotiation.
And they're much stronger than us.
If we fight them,
there's no doubt we'll all be killed.
Wouldn't it be better to lose
one person than all of us?
Y-Yeah! That's right.
Ikeuchi, you're so brave.
--Huh?
--You've accepted the fact that
you might be the one who's chosen.
You really are brave.
What? Hang on...
If we fight, we know we'll all die.
If we decide to offer a sacrifice,
then won't the person that gets chosen
be someone that agreed to the sacrifice?
She's out of the running...
So does that mean the one that's chosen...
...will be me?!
Was that too much for you?
If you're not prepared,
you shouldn't say reckless things like that.
Clair...
Either way, I'm dead.
Madoka, what's up?
Are you thinking about something?
Nah... It's just... I'm having so much fun.
I never thought a piece of shit
like me would be living this way.
Nothing I did ever went right.
I never got along with anyone.
My eyes were always on the ground...
Although I guess that's how
I ended up finding the coin, so...
We're all the same.
Everyone that's here is here
because there's nowhere else for them.
Yeah...
Being surrounded by
a bunch of shitheads like you...
Well, nothing has ever made me happier.
Uh... Um... I've got an idea.
Let's hear it.
I'll turn invisible and assassinate their boss.
As long as he hasn't transformed,
I think I can do it.
You all can run during the commotion.
No. We can't just leave you behind like--
Right, that's not bad.
I didn't give you enough credit.
You've got guts, don't you?
But they might have someone on their
side that has special sight, like Ikeuchi.
Being invisible isn't necessarily enough.
But...
Clair's right. And if we kill him,
we'll be no better than him.
So what should we do?
Think... Think! Maybe I can
hold them off while everyone runs...
What happened to Isao?
He said he wanted to be alone.
How are your injuries?
I won't do it.
I can't offer up a friend.
I know. I just wanted everyone to be aware...
Aware of how dangerous this situation is...
I'm useless...
We're in this terrible situation,
and I can't help.
That's not true. You have a wonderful power.
I want you to grow this here.
Is that--?!
Please...
Use your power to save us.
Clair?
What is this...?
Sorry for the weird request, Isao.
They are lovely, though.
What are all these flowers...?
Shuichi, great timing.
We've just finished
preparations for our escape--
Can you tell everyone?
Escape?
Thank you, Isao.
I'll handle the rest.
Isao...?
These flowers are... Yes. She's crazy!
Yoshioka... I'll protect you, no matter what!
These beautiful flowers have an ominous scent.
But I know.
Clair's actions are always based in logic.
Clair... Is there anything I can do?
No.
I'm about to do something terrible.
You're a good kid, so stay out of it, okay?
Clair...
You must realize by now--
There are a lot of people up here,
and some of them are too far gone.
When you're dealing with them,
you're going to have to get your hands dirty.
That's what I'm here for.
I can do things that you
and our other friends can't.
Special powers, incredible strength--
these things aren't scary.
What's scary is the people who use those powers.
Let me do it.
Even I know how dangerous
our situation is right now.
I want to protect them! I'm ready for it!
No.
I don't want you to carry
the burden of any more crimes.
Even if it's wrong...
...we two are one.
When someone takes action
for the sake of another,
even the most pure-hearted
person can turn completely ruthless.
It must have been that way with her, too.
They got away? Why weren't you watching them?!
Sorry! I didn't think they'd run!
I took my eyes off them, and then...
Huh?
Wait! Get out of here!
I'm abandoning them!
Me and the girl, Yoshioka! Let us join you!
What? Where the hell did that come from?
Hey, over there!
Huh?
It's burning! They set the mountain on fire!
One last futile struggle, huh?
That's a pretty big fire.
Isao! What were the flowers you grew back there?
It's oleander.
Is that some kind of special plant?
No, it grows all over the place.
The flowers are grown
in private gardens and parks.
Although not many people know...
...oleander is a powerful poison.
And that poison isn't just
in its leaves and flowers--
It's in its smoke, too.
Damn... It's over!
What are you blabbering about?
This is serious, okay?!
One of my friends used
their ability to grow these flow--
Did he just die on his own?
What the hell is up with him?
What're you going to do, Madoka?
It's obvious, isn't it?
Kill them all.
Yoshioka! Aihara! Are you okay?
Hang on tight!
Here we go!
Thank you!
Let's get out of this forest!
Hang on a second.
I feel kind of sick.
Me, too.
I feel nauseous, too.
Madoka! We're in trouble!
The fire is getting bigger and bigger!
What the hell?
Are those flowers poisonous?
We have to get out of here!
Even if it's just those of us that can move!
You guys go ahead.
What are you saying?! First the leader ha--
You idiot!
Did you... forget...?!
Whatever happens...
...I will not abandon you!
Madoka,
I'll help!
--Me too!
Did you consider that
he might have headed straight here
before getting caught up in the smoke?
Yeah.
If he had, that would have been the end of us.
I just bet that he wouldn't.
I bet that he'd try to save his friends.
I told you...
Special powers, incredible strength--
these things aren't scary.
What's scary is the people who use those powers.
You're starting to scare me, Clair.
At first, I thought you
were just someone I could trust.
Now I have no idea what you're thinking.
I'm not sure about Elena, either.
It's hard to believe
she could be a murderous demon.
I used to think that
was totally ridiculous, but...
I was the same way.
I could never figure out why
she gave me the coin that day.
But ever since I met Shuichi,
I kind of feel like I might know...
Know what my sister wanted from me.
She couldn't bare the weight of her crimes...
But she couldn't run from them, either.
Clair...
I guess that's how it had to be.
I'm the only one who can save her.
Hey, it's been a while.
Well? How's the coin search going?
"Episode 11: The Price of Resolve"